A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants Them-Tw FA732H FA732H
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - Them to Tw, 1937-2006
  - The University Of Chicago (07350347), 1973 March 13-1973 December 31 (Reel R1221)
    PRELIMINARY FEASIBILITY STUDY FOR A RESEARCH PROGRAM ON ISLAM AND SOCIAL CHANGE
  - The University Of Chicago (07400141), 1973 December 20-1978 December 31 (Reel R3087)
    RESEARCH ON ISLAM AND SOCIAL CHANGE
    Asia & The Pacific [ASIA];Africa & The Middle East [AME]
    Carmichael, William D.(William Daniel);Geithner, Peter F.
    Middle East; South Asia; SouthEast Asia; Africa, North
  - The University Of Chicago (07400203), 1974 October 01-1980 June 30 (Reel R2190, Reel R2299)
    SUPPORT FOR TRAINING AND RESEARCH PROGRAMS IN THE ECONOMICS AND POLITICS OF PUBLIC SCHOOL FINANCE
    $146,000.00;$146,000.00
  - The University Of Chicago (07500503), 1975 August 01-1979 July 31 (Reel R3635)
  - The University Of Chicago (07500536), 1975 June 01-1976 December 31 (Reel R2618)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON FLEXIBLE EXCHANGE RATE REGIMES AND CAPITALMOBILITY
    $50,010.00;$50,010.00
  - The University Of Chicago (07550459), 1975 July 14-1982 June 30 (Reel R2839, Reel R2840)
    SUPPORT OF A CONFERENCE OF THE COMMITTEE FOR COMPARATIVE STUDY OF NEW NATIONS TO BE HELD IN CHICAGO, OCTOBER 16-19, 1975
    Geithner, Peter F.;Sutton, Francis X. (Francis Xavier)
  - The University Of Chicago (07550523), 1975 July 01-1977 June 30 (Reel R1272)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR DEVELOPMENT OF A JOINT CITY/ UNIVERSITY URBAN POLICY PROGRAM
  - The University Of Chicago (07600116), 1975 January 01-1980 April 01 (Reel R2779)
    FELLOWSHIPS FOR TRAINING IN COMMUNICATIONS FOR CANDIDATES FROM LDC INSTITUTIONS AT THE COMMUNITY AND FAMILY STUDY CENTER
    Population [POP];Office of Communications (pre 1979)
    $109,300.00;$43,392.35
    Harkavy, Oscar;Meade, Edward J.
  - The University Of Chicago (07600222), 1976 March 18-1977 August 29 (Reel R3043, Reel R4103)
    ENDOWMENT FUND FOR SUPPORT OF THE ADLAI E. STEVENSON CENTER
    $146,993.9;$146,993.9
  - The University Of Chicago (07600412), 1976 July 01-1977 May 31 (Reel R1402)
    RESEARCH PROJECT ON ROLE OF PRIVATE PHILANTHROPY IN FORMULATING PUBLIC POLICY
    $16,354.00;$16,354.00
    Hertz, Willard J.
  - The University Of Chicago (07750123), 1977 January 01-1977 December 31 (Reel R1228)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE PUBLICATION OF AN HISTORICAL ATLAS OF SOUTH BY THE UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO PRESS
  - The University Of Chicago (07750141), 1977 January 18-1978 January 17 (Reel R1969)
    SUPPORT FOR AN EXPANDED ISSUE OF SIGNS
  - The University Of Chicago (07750261), 1977 April 01-1978 March 31 (Reel R2438)
    SUPPORT FOR A SEMINAR ON TEACHERS' CENTER TO BE HELD JUNE 19 21, 1977
    $22,880.00;$22,880.00
  - The University Of Chicago (07800049), 1977 November 01-1982 October 31 (Reel R4220)
    SUPPORT OF CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT AND RELATED PUBLIC POLICY TRAINING ACTIVITIES OF THE COMMITTEE ON PUBLIC POLICY STUDIES
  - The University Of Chicago (07800541), 1978 September 01-1981 August 31 (Reel R5195)
  - The University Of Chicago (07850011), 1977 October 01-1981 October 01 (Reel R4091)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR PUBLICATION COSTS OF HERBERT STORING'S "THE COMPLETE ANTI-FEDERALIST PAPERS"
  - The University Of Chicago (07850683), 1978 September 08-1979 September 07 (Reel R2186)
    SUPPORT FOR THE ADDITION OF LATIN AMERICAN MATERIAL TO AN ISSUE OF "SIGNS"
    $4,600.00;$4,600.00
  - The University of Chicago (08000367), 1980 March 01-1981 July 31 (Reel R3731, Reel R4053)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF PUBLIC POLICY AND SERVICES FOR CHILDREN IN ILLINOIS
    $25,000.00;$24,951.13
  - The University of Chicago (08000546), 1980 September 01-1984 June 30 (Reel R6691)
    SUPPORT OF RESEARCH AND TRAINING ON DOMESTIC AGRICULTURE IN THE DEPARTMENT OF ECONOMICS
    $51,700.00;$51,700.00
  - The University of Chicago (08050511), 1980 May 15-1981 May 14 (Reel R4093)
    FOR GENERAL SUPPORT OF THE CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF WELFARE POLICY
    $15,000.00;$14,890.17
  - The University of Chicago (08150079), 1980 October 15-1981 January 14 (Reel R3096)
    RESEARCH AND TRAVEL RELATING TO THE CHINESE RURAL ECONOMY
    $2,150.00;$2,147.00
  - The University of Chicago (08150183), 1981 January 01-1981 December 31 (Reel R3739)
    SUPPORT OF A ONE DAY CONFERENCE ON "THE ENVIRONMENTS OF HUMAN SERVICE MANAGEMENT"
  - The University of Chicago (08150190), 1980 December 01-1981 November 30 (Reel R4347)
    SUPPORT TO THE UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO PRESS FOR PUBLICATION OF THE BOOK, "EDUCATIONAL CHOICE AND LABOR MARKETS IN JAPAN"
  - The University of Chicago (08250638), 1982 May 01-1983 April 30 (Reel R4045)
    SUPPORT FOR TRAINING IN FIELD ARCHAEOLOGY FOR SRI LANKAN UNIVERSITY STUDENTS AT THE MANTAI EXCAVATIONS IN SRI LANKA
    Joshi, V. C.
  - The University of Chicago (08250821), 1982 July 01-1983 June 30 (Reel R3727)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A CONFERENCE ON GOLD AND THE EVOLVING INTERNATIONAL FINANCIAL ARRANGEMENTS
  - The University of Chicago (08400734), 1984 September 01-1987 August 31 (Reel R6036)
    PROVIDE PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR HARPER POSTDOCTORAL TEACHING PROGRAM IN THE HUMANITIES AND SOCIAL SCIENCES
    $300,000.00;$299,645.72
  - The University of Chicago (08450530), 1984 January 01-1989 December 31 (Reel R6010)
    SUPPORT FOR STUDY ENTITLED "NORMAL NEEDS & UNCONVENTIONAL HELPING"
    $27,450.00;$27,410.29
  - The University of Chicago (08500087), 1984 June 01-1986 August 31 (Reel R5276)
    SUPPORT WORKSHOP & SPECIALISTS' CONFERENCE ON ETHICAL IMPLICATIONS OF NUCLEAR WEAPONS & THEIR USE & FOR A SPECIAL ISSUE OF "ETHICS"
  - The University of Chicago (08501035), 1985 October 01-1988 September 30 (Reel R5621)
    RESEARCH PROJECT ON "POVERTY AND FAMILY STRUCTURE IN THE INNER CITY" (WELFARE STATE 36 PERCENT)
  - The University of Chicago (08600318), 1986 March 15-1991 December 31 (Reel R6263)
    PROTOTYPE PROGRAM FOR THE PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT OF COMMUNITY COLLEGE TEACHERS OF WRITING
    $185,621.00;$185,621.00
  - The University of Chicago (08650439), 1986 April 16-1988 August 22 (Reel R5493, Reel R5757)
    SUPPORT FOR CONFERENCE ON CONSERVATION OF CULTURE AND ENVIRONMENT IN RAJASTHAN
    $42,305.00;$42,305.00
  - The University of Chicago (08700699), 1987 July 01-1991 June 30 (Reel R6203)
    TO IMPROVE THE QUALITY OF UNDERGRADUATE EDUCATION AND INTEREST STUDENTS IN FACULTY CAREERS/RESEARCH SEMINARS IN THE COLLEGE
  - The University of Chicago (08700902), 1987 September 01-1990 August 31 (Reel R6035)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR TWO SUMMER SCHOOL PROGRAMS FOR LOOP COLLEGE STUDENTS AT THE UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO
    $119,000.00;$96,091.40
  - The University of Chicago (08750060), 1986 October 01-1986 December 31 (Reel R5271)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ENTITLED "A SEARCH FOR SOLUTIONS:USA - USSR"
  - The University of Chicago (08800412), 1988 June 01-1991 September 30 (Reel R6209)
    FOR AMERICAN-SWISS COLLABORATION ON RESEARCH CONCERNING "SECURITY & ECONOMICS IN ALLIANCE POLITICS: LINKAGE, LEADERSHIP & STABILITY"
    Switzerland; United States
  - The University of Chicago (08800943), 1988 June 01-1997 June 30 (Reel R7197)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF THE IMPACT OF THE SOUTHERN DEV'T BANCORPORATION'S PROGRAMS ON ECONOMIC GROWTH IN RURAL ARKANSAS
    Arkansas
  - The University of Chicago (08800948), 1988 September 01-1999 August 31 (Reel R8649)
    IMPROVE THE TEACHING OF THE SOCIAL SCIENCES AT THE UNDERGRADUATE LEVEL (006)
    Balan, Jorge;Beckham, Edgar F.;Volkman, Toby Alice
  - The University of Chicago (08850482), 1987 November 01-1988 October 31 (Reel R5812, Reel R5979)
    SUPPORT FOR AN EPIGRAPHER WORKING ON LUXOR INSCRIPTIONS
    $4,800.00;$4,800.00
  - The University of Chicago (08900017), 1988 August 01-1995 December 31 (Reel R8026)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON HOUSING REVITALIZATION ACTIVITIES IN A LOW INCOME CHICAGO NEIGHBORHOOD
    $338,000.00;$338,000.00
  - The University of Chicago (08900247), 1989 January 01-1990 September 30 (Reel R5991)
    SUPPORT FOR A POSTDOCTORAL FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM FOR POLISH SOCIOLOGISTS AT AMERICAN UNIVERSITIES (009)
    $118,048.00;$118,048.00
  - The University of Chicago (08951046), 1989 June 01-1991 January 31 (Reel R6262)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF THE IMPACT OF STATE HIGHER EDUCATION STRUCTURE ON THE RATE OF BACHELOR'S DEGREE ATTAINMENT
    $47,000.00;$47,000.00
  - The University of Chicago (08951226), 1989 September 01-1991 March 31 (Reel R6422)
    SUPPORT FOR PROJECT-RELATED TRAVEL TO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CORPORATIONS
    $6,500.00;$6,500.00
  - The University of Chicago (09001487), 1990 September 01-1994 August 31 (Reel R7080)
    SUPPORT FOR J.D. & GRADUATE FELLOWSHIPS & INTERNSHIPS & AN INTERNATIONAL LAW WORKSHOP AT THE CHICAGO SCHOOL OF LAW (011)
    $205,000.00;$199,637.12
  - The University of Chicago (09051261), 1990 September 01-1992 August 31 (Reel R6629)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON "EUROPE 1992: THE LEGAL RESTRUCTURING OF THE EUROPEAN COMMUNITY"
  - The University of Chicago (09100172), 1990 November 01-1997 December 31 (Reel R7657)
    SUPPORT FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF A COMPREHENSIVE NEIGHBORHOOD REVITALIZATION MODEL AND EVALUATION STRATEGY
    $1,935,012.00;$1,935,012.00
    Kubisch, Anne C.;Mincy, Ronald B.;Anglin, Roland;Molnar, Janice M.
    United States; Detroit (Mich.); Hartford (Conn.); Memphis (Tenn.)
  - The University of Chicago (09101378), 1991 September 01-1992 March 31 (Reel R6497)
  - The University of Chicago (09150549), 1991 April 01-1991 September 30 (Reel R6840)
    SUPPORT FOR A WORKING PAPER ON COMPREHENSIVE COMMUNITY-BASED SERVICES.
  - The University of Chicago (09201151), 1992 October 01-1996 June 30 (Reel R7324)
    SUPPORT TO PURSUE ANALYTIC AND DEVELOPMENTAL ACTIVITIES IN THE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT AND HUMAN SERVICE FIELDS
  - The University of Chicago (09201299), 1992 September 01-1996 June 30 (Reel R7638, Reel R8157)
    CORE SUPPORT FOR THE CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF URBAN INEQUALITY
    Brown, Prudence;Diaz, William A.
    United States; Chicago (Ill.)
  - The University of Chicago (09201371), 1992 October 01-1993 September 30 (Reel R6826)
    SUPPORT FOR A SURVEY OF RESIDENTS IN TWO NEIGHBORHOOD AND FAMILY INITIATIVE SITES
    United States; Hartford (Conn.); Memphis (Tenn.)
  - The University of Chicago (09250960), 1992 August 01-1994 December 31 (Reel R6951)
    SUPPORT FOR RUSSIAN, BALTIC & UKRAINIAN PARTICIPATION IN WORK OF CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF CONSTITUTIONALISM IN EASTERN EUROPE (009)
    $167,000.00;$167,000.00
  - The University of Chicago (09300591), 1993 April 01-1995 March 31 (Reel R6806)
    SUPPORT FOR SURVEY OF ADULT SEXUAL BEHAVIOR
  - The University of Chicago (09301193), 1993 July 01-2001 June 30 (Reel R9041)
  - The University of Chicago (09401417), 1994 October 01-1996 December 31 (Reel R7344)
    SUPPORT FOR A MODEL SEXUALITY RESEARCH INITIATIVE IN CHICAGO
    $430,300.00;$430,300.00
  - The University of Chicago (09500382), 1995 January 01-2000 December 31 (Reel R8431)
    SUPPORT TO MAKE ACCESSIBLE THE ROJA MUTHIAH COLLECTION OF TAMIL LANGUAGE MATERIALS ON PERFORMANCE AND FOLKLORE
  - The University of Chicago (09500506), 1995 January 01-1997 June 30 (Reel R7422, Reel R7808)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR WORK ON LEGAL AND CONSTITUTIONAL REFORM BY THE CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF CONSTITUTIONALISM IN EASTERN EUROPE
    $360,000.00;$360,000.00
  - The University of Chicago (09551459), 1995 October 01-1997 June 30 (Reel R7445)
    SUPPORT FOR A PILOT PROGRAM EXPLORING THE LINKS BETWEEN AREA STUDIES AND CULTURAL STUDIES
  - The University of Chicago (09600474), 1996 March 01-1998 February 28 (Reel R8130)
    SUPPORT FOR WRITING AND PUBLICATION OF STUDIES ON THE INVOLVEMENT OF DISADVANTAGED FATHERS IN THE LIVES OF DISADVANTAGED FAMILIES
  - The University of Chicago (09700155), 1996 October 01-2000 September 30 (Reel R8659)
    SUPPORT FOR A SEXUALITY RESEARCH PROGRAM IN CHICAGO (940-1417)
  - The University of Chicago (09700591), 1997 March 01-2000 September 30 (Reel R8752)
    SUPPORT FOR CONTINUED EVALUATION OF NFI (910-0172)
    Floyd, Virginia Davis;Roman, Ruth
    Detroit (Mich.); Hartford (Conn.); Memphis (Tenn.); Milwaukee (Wis.); Community development, Urban --United States -- Evaluation
  - The University of Chicago (09700855), 1997 March 01-2002 June 30 (Reel R9131)
    SUPPORT FOR "REGIONAL WORLDS: A NEW APPROACH TO AREA STUDIES"
    $348,000.00;$348,000.00
  - The University of Chicago (09700951), 1997 March 01-1999 September 30 (Reel R8439)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF CAPACITY BUILDING IN COMMUNITY CHANGE EFFORTS
  - The University of Chicago (09750412), 1997 January 01-1997 December 31 (Reel R7579)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF THE IMPACT OF THE SOUTHERN DEVELOPMENT BANCORPORATION'S PROGRAMS ON ECONOMIC GROWTH IN RURAL ARKANSAS(880-0943)
  - The University of Chicago (09801669), 1998 August 01-2003 June 30 (Reel R9206)
    SUPPORT FOR STUDY OF ORGANIZATIONAL RESPONSE TO LOW WAGE AND WELFARE WORKERS IN CORPORATIONS, NONPROFIT AND GOVERNMENT AGENCIES
    Human Rights;Governance and Civil Society;Human Development and Reproductive Health
    United States; Public policy--United States; Welfare recipients--Employment--United States
  - The University of Chicago (09900540), 1999 March 01-2002 September 30 (Reel R8980)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF AFRICAN-AMERICAN CIVIL SOCIETY
    Vaid, Urvashi
    United States; Civil society -- Study and teaching -- United States; African Americans -- Social conditions; Civil society -- United States -- Citizen participation
  - The University of Chicago (09901402), 1999 July 01-2000 June 30 (Reel R8423)
    SUPPORT FOR ANALYSIS OF NEWLY RELEASED DATA ON YOUTH DEVELOPMENT AND FOR A RELATED NATIONAL CONFERENCE
    United States; Youth--Research--United States; Fathers -- Research -- United States; Poverty--Research--United States
  - The University of Chicago (10000113), 2000 January 01-2002 December 31 (Reel R9077)
    RESEARCH PROJECT TO STUDY THE CHARACTER AND DYNAMICS OF TRANSNATIONAL ADVOCACY-ORIENTED CIVIL SOCIETY NETWORKS, INCLUDING THE GLOBAL FORMATIONS OF GRASSROOTS GROUPS
    Global; Community development -- Global -- Citizen participation; Community development -- India -- Citizen participation; Community development -- Netherlands -- Citizen participation
  - The University of Chicago (10050992), 2000 July 01-2001 January 31 (Reel R8932)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR AN INTRNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON GAY AND LESBIAN HISTORY
    $55,000.00;$47,781.45
    United States; Gay rights -- History -- Congresses; Lesbians; Gay men
  - The University of Chicago (10151465), 2001 July 01-2004 July 31 (Reel R9196)
    To provide technical assistance to the Foundation's Constituency Building for Public School Reform Initiative through the Chapin Hall Center for Children
    $153,100.00;$153,100.00
    United States; Educational equalization -- United States; Education -- Aims and objectives
  - The University Of Connecticut (05600196), 1956 June 25-1957 June 24 (Reel R0065)
  - The University Of Connecticut (05900099), 1959 January 28-1960 January 27 (Reel R0234)
    RESEARCH ON MEASUREMENT IN MARKETING
    $4,750.00;$4,750.00
  - The University Of Connecticut (06000228), 1960 May 26-1961 May 25 (Reel R0211)
    ACTIVATE EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION CHANNELS
    $34,550.00;$34,550.00
  - The University Of Connecticut (06400137), 1964 January 09-1969 January 08 (Reel R2251)
    STRENGTHENING OF THE DEPARTMENT OF ECONOMICS AS A RESOURCE FOR OVERSEAS CONSULATION AND TRAINING
    Bloom, Clark C.
  - The University Of Connecticut (06900089), 1968 December 02-1969 December 01 (Reel R1593)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A UNIVERSITY-WIDE PROGRAM ON THE 1930'S
    $30,000.00;$29,966.40
  - The University Of Connecticut (06900449), 1969 May 29-1970 May 28 (Reel R1944)
    $14,950.00;$14,950.00
  - The University Of Connecticut (07000368), 1970 June 12-1971 December 11 (Reel R1697)
    $20,512.00;$20,512.00
  - The University Of Connecticut (07100229), 1971 September 01-1972 August 31 (Reel R1728)
    DISSERTATION FELLOWSHIP IN ETHNIC STUDIES FOR MR. LAWRENCE ANTHONY CARDOSO & MRS. TAMAH L. SADICK
    $9,978.00;$5,000.00
  - The University of Connecticut (08850028), 1987 December 01-1992 September 30 (Reel R6338)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY ON THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN GROUNDWATER CONTAMINATION AND AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTION
    $49,250.00;$49,250.00
  - The University Of Delhi (05500164), 1955 July 01-1961 September 30 (Reel R0668, Reel R0669, Reel R3919)
    TO SUPPORT A PROFESSORSHIP IN AMERICAN CIVILIZATION AND SOCIAL-POLITICAL INSTITUTIONS
    $238,000.00;$238,000.00
  - The University Of Delhi (05800058), 1958 January 08-1963 January 07 (Reel R0905, Reel R3224, Reel R3225)
    PRECEPTORIAL AND TUTORIAL STUDIES
    $426,000.00;$426,000.00
  - The University Of Delhi (05800124), 1958 March 31-1965 September 30 (Reel R0479, Reel R3225)
    PROGRAM IN INTERNATIONAL LAW
    $151,000.00;$131,460.18
  - The University Of Delhi (06200470), 1962 September 24-1968 June 24 (Reel R2569, Reel R3211)
    INSTITUTIONAL SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND TRAINING IN REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY IN INDIA
    Bunker, Samuel E.
    Scope and Contents
    Includes material on Dr. Katherine Kuder.
    File Plan
    PA62-470
  - The University Of Delhi (06400268), 1964 May 15-1965 November 14 (Reel R0924, Reel R3315)
    ESTABLISHMENT OF A PLANNING UNIT
    $21,000.00;$18,652.69
  - The University Of Delhi (06400272), 1964 May 15-1965 May 14 (Reel R0925)
    PROVISION OF ELECTRONIC DATA PROCESSING EQUIPMENT FOR RESEARCH IN ECONOMICS, AGRICULTURE AND DEMOGRAPHY
    $371,000.00;$360,999.15
  - The University Of Delhi (06400465), 1964 September 09-1971 May 31 (Reel R1611, Reel R3459, Reel R3460)
    DEVELOPMENT OF A PROGRAM OF RESEARCH AND TRAINING IN CHINESE STUDIES AT THE UNIVERSITY IN INDIA
    $536,000.00;$531,629.21
    China; India
  - The University Of Delhi (06700143), 1967 March 13-1971 March 13 (Reel R1828, Reel R3461)
    SUPPORT OF LAW FACULTY AT THE UNIVERSITY
    $441,000.00;$297,956.44
    Bunker, Samuel E.;Frodin, Reuben
  - The University Of Delhi (06700444), 1967 July 21-1970 December 31 (Reel R1312, Reel R1313, Reel R3462)
    STRENGTHENING TEACHING AND RESEARCH AT THE UNIVERSITY
    $1,500,000.00;$1,264,361.93
    Edwards, Edgar O.;Frodin, Reuben
  - The University Of Delhi (06800044), 1967 November 29-1970 November 28 (Reel R2690, Reel R3462, Reel R3463)
    LIBRARY DEVELOPMENT
    $351,000.00;$240,477.82
    Frodin, Reuben;Wilhelm, Harry E.
  - The University Of Delhi (06900146), 1969 January 14-1974 January 13 (Reel R1262, Reel R4294)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ACTIVITIES IN REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY
    $74,500.00;$72,247.12
  - The University Of Delhi (06900614), 1969 August 13-1974 March 31 (Reel R2167, Reel R3483, Reel R3484)
    FACULTY EXCHANGE PROGRAM TO STRENGTHEN TEACHING AND RESEARCH AT THE UNIVERSITY
    $450,000.00;$115,229.36
  - The University Of Delhi (07000330), 1970 May 22-1972 May 21 (Reel R1138, Reel R3486, Reel R3487)
    PURCHASE OF IBM 360/44 COMPUTER SYSTEM AND ADVICE ON ESTABLISHMENT OF COMPUTER CENTER
    $644,000.00;$601,558.97
  - The University Of Delhi (07200117), 1972 February 09-1982 March 31 (Reel R4066, Reel R4425, Reel R4426)
    DEVELOPMENTAL SUPPORT FOR THE UNIVERSITY
    $2,438,000.00;$2,438,000.00
    Elliott, Carolyn M.
  - The University of Delhi (08900591), 1989 June 23-1996 June 30 (Reel R7238)
    SUPPORT TO IMPROVE THE CAPACITY OF COMMUNITIES TO MANAGE VILLAGE COMMONS AND STATE FOREST LANDS
    $50,000.00;$25,000.00
  - The University of Delhi (09051281), 1990 August 01-1991 August 01 (Reel R6151)
    SUPPORT FOR STRENGTHENING THE RESOURCES OF RATAN TATA LIBRARY OF THE DELHI SCHOOL OF ECONOMICS
  - The University of Delhi (09801195), 1998 August 18-2002 October 31 (Reel R9039)
    BUILDING CAPACITY FOR GENDER RELATED RESEARCH AND ACTION ON WATER RESOURCES THROUGH COLLABORATIVE RESEARCH, TRAINING, AND NETWORKING
    $60,000.00;$51,026.38
    India; Water resources development--India; Conservation of natural resources--India; Women in development--India
  - The University of Delhi (10251675), 2002 August 19-2005 August 18 (Reel R9280)
    For the Millennium Lectures to bring outstanding international scholars from a broad range of disciplines to the university for a series of public lectures
    $45,000.00;$36,786.16
  - The University Of East Anglia (07100050), 1970 December 01-1975 November 30 (Reel R1433)
    SUPPORT FOR FIVE ENVIRONMENTAL SEMINARS
  - The University Of East Anglia (07300180), 1972 September 01-1979 August 31 (Reel R2236)
    RESEARCH PROJECTS IN TEACHING METHODS AND EVALUATING INNOVATIVE PROCESSES IN SCHOOLS AT CENTRE FOR APPLIED RESEARCH IN EDUCATION
    $155,000.00;$151,916.00
  - The University Of East Anglia (07450691), 1974 October 01-1975 December 31 (Reel R2427)
    RESEARCH PROJECTS ON TEACHING METHODS AND EVALUATING INNOVATIVE PROCESSES AT THE CENTRE FOR APPLIED RESEARCH IN EDUCATION
  - The University Of East Anglia (07850483), 1978 July 01-1980 February 28 (Reel R2117)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON CLIMATE AND HISTORY
    $12,000.00;$11,899.40
  - The University Of East Anglia (07900698), 1979 October 01-1980 October 15 (Reel R2440)
    PRODUCTION OF A CASE STUDY OF BILINGUAL SCHOOLING
  - The University of East Anglia (08250805), 1982 July 01-1982 September 30 (Reel R3555)
    SUPPORT TO REPRODUCE AND DISSEMINATE REPORT OF A FOUNDATION- SUPPORTED STUDY OF BILINGUAL EDUCATION IN BOSTON
    Boston (Mass.)
  - The University of East Anglia (08300775), 1983 September 09-1987 July 31 (Reel R5338)
    SUPPORT FOR MULTIDISCIPLINARY-ON FARM RESEARCH TO DEVELOP RICE TECHNOLOGIES FOR RESOURCE-POOR FARMERS IN EASTERN INDIA
    Bottrall, Anthony
  - The University of East Anglia (08550060), 1984 September 01-1987 March 31 (Reel R5787, Reel R5966)
    SUPPORT FOR WORK ON FARMING SYSTEMS RESEARCH TO BE CARRIED OUT IN COLLABORATION WITH THE BANGLADESH AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH COUNCIL
    $49,778.00;$49,778.00
  - The University of East Anglia (09000310), 1990 February 01-1993 June 01 (Reel R6748)
    SUPPORT FOR AIDS RESEARCH, TRAINING AND DISSEMINATION IN KENYA
    $117,200.00;$117,200.00
    Bailey, Charles R.;Bangser, Maggie A.
  - The University of East Anglia (09100726), 1991 January 01-1993 October 31 (Reel R6338)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND EDUCATION ON THE IMPACT OF CLIMATE CHANGE ON BANGLADESH
    $100,000.00;$.00
  - The University Of Hartford (06400318), 1964 July 08-1966 July 07 (Reel R0224)
    $6,343.00;$6,042.01
  - The University Of Hartford (07500303), 1975 April 01-1979 October 31 (Reel R4978)
    SUPPORT OF THE UNIVERSITY'S NATIONAL EDUCATION STRATEGY CENTER
    $320,911.00;$320,911.00
    Connecticut
  - The University Of Hartford (07800883), 1978 November 01-1983 June 30 (Reel R4806)
    SUPPORT FOR INSTITUTIONAL PROJECT TO IMPROVE EDUCATIONAL SERVICE TO POOR AND DISADVANTAGED PEOPLE
    $155,200.00;$155,200.00
    Hartford (Conn.)
  - The University Of Kansas (05500146), 1955 June 17-1956 June 16 (Reel R0065)
  - The University Of Kansas (05600033), 1956 January 04-1957 January 03 (Reel R0019)
    PROVIDE ASSISTANCE FOR COMPLETION OF WORK ON THE THEORY OF INTERPERSONAL RELATIONS %STUDY
  - The University Of Kansas (05600059), 1956 February 21-1961 February 20 (Reel R0015)
  - The University Of Kansas (05700251), 1957 June 24-1959 April 15 (Reel R0065)
    $1,931.00;$1,931.00
  - The University Of Kansas (05800012), 1957 October 31-1961 October 01 (Reel R0143)
    STATE CONSTITUTIONAL STUDIES
    $25,000.00;$24,785.77
  - The University Of Kansas (05800133), 1958 March 31-1963 August 31 (Reel R0168)
    INTER-UNIVERSITY SOCIAL SCIENCE FACULTY SEMINAR ON URBANIZATION IN MISSOURI RIVER BASIN AREA
    $39,600.00;$37,871.71
  - The University Of Kansas (05800215), 1958 May 26-1963 May 25 (Reel R0346)
    COOPERATIVE RESEARCH ON COMMUNIST MOVEMENT IN PRE-WAR JAPAN
    $5,700.00;$5,700.00